



KARAN PARMAR

Software Developer



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a Software Developer. I have a strong knowledge of coding languages such as Java, JavaScript. I have worked on multiple projects involving designing, coding and debugging software applications to ensure they meet customer requirements. My biggest achievements include developing a web-based application using ReactJs, MongoDB, ExpressJs, NodeJs.

in karan-parmar9186

Karan9186

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Application

Ganpat University / India, Mehsana -Sem 4- 8.65 CGPA

SKILLS

JavaScript	Expert
HTML/CSS	Expert
Java + DSA	Skillful
 ReactJs 	Experienced
NodeJs	Experienced
MongoDb	Experienced
ExpressJs	Experienced
PL/SQL	Experienced
• PHP	Experienced
JQuery	Skillful
 Bootstrap 	Experienced
Tailwind	Skillful

COURSES

Java + DSA

Apna College

Generative AI

LinkedIn

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Gujarati

EXPERIENCE

2023 - 2023

web developer intern

remote

As a web developer intern at remote

- · Developed and maintained websites using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript,-
- · Conducted quality assurance testing to ensure functionality and user experience

2023 - 2023

web developer intern

remote

During my time as a web developer intern at Remote.

- · Improved communication and time management skills
- Implemented new features on website
- · Conducted regular website testing and troubleshooting
- · Assisted in creating responsive designs for mobile devices

2024 - 2024

freelance full stack developer remote

As a freelance full stack developer at a remote. I was responsible for creating and maintaining websites and applications. Working remotely allowed me to collaborate with clients from various industries and locations, honing my communication and problem-solving skills.

- · Integrated APIs and databases to enhance functionality
- · Communicated regularly with clients to understand their needs
- Successfully delivered projects within tight deadlines